{
    "subject": "resource/Ari_Up",
    "predicate": "ontology/birthDate",
    "object": "1962-01-17",
    "human_readable": "Ari Up was born on January 17, 1962.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8447057604789734,
            "question": "When was Ari Up born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7681974172592163,
            "question": "If today was January 17th, would it be Ari Up's birthday?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7312209606170654,
            "question": "Is Ari Up's birthdate known?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.701499879360199,
            "question": "What month was Ari Up born in?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5436259508132935,
            "question": "Besides birthdate, what other details might be helpful to know about Ari Up?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.44623664021492004,
            "question": "In what year did Ari Up come into the world?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.29136180877685547,
            "question": "Can we determine Ari Up's age based on the given information?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.24635694921016693,
            "question": "What information is given about Ari Up in this set of facts?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.23460526764392853,
            "question": "How could we find out more about Ari Up's life?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.020262252539396286,
            "question": "What kind of facts are typically included in a biography?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Ari Up was born on January 17, 1962.",
            "html": "dbpedia_2331_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=How could we find out more about Ari Up's life?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2331_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What information is given about Ari Up in this set of facts?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2331_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can we determine Ari Up's age based on the given information?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2331_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2331_14.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2331_19.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2331_37.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2331_41.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2331_42.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2331_43.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2331_51.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2331_7.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2331_76.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2331_93.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\nThis answer is derived from the information provided in the documents, which state that Ari Up was born on January 17, 1962."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Least Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}